<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="100">
    <author>Ozz</author>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>
    <iconFilename>icon_HirePurchasing.dds</iconFilename>
    <title>
        <en>Hire Purchasing</en>
        <de>Mietkauf</de>
        <fr>Location-Achat</fr>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[Hire Purchasing

A mod that adds an option to purchase equipment through a hire purchase model.

- Purchase equipment by putting down a configurable deposit. A higher deposit will reduce the interest rate.
- Choose how long your agreement should last.
- Choose from four payment plans, each with different monthly payments and final fees.
- Settle your agreement early to save on interest costs.

]]>
        </en>
        <de><![CDATA[Mietkauf

Ein Mod, der eine Option zum Kauf von Ausrüstung über ein Ratenkaufmodell hinzufügt.

- Kaufe Ausrüstung mit einer konfigurablem Anzahlung. Eine höhere Anzahlung reduziert den Zinseszins.
- Wähle die Dauer deines Vertrags.
- Wähle aus vier Zahlungsplänen, jedes mit unterschiedlichen monatlichen Zahlungen und Endgebühren.
- Setze deinen Vertrag früh ab, um auf Zinskosten zu sparen.

]]>
        </de>
        <fr><![CDATA[Location-Achat

Un mod qui ajoute une option d'achat d'équipement via un modèle de location-vente.

- Achetez des équipements en payant une cautionnable caution. Une plus grande caution réduit le taux d'intérêt.
- Choisissez la durée de votre accord.
- Choisissez parmi quatre plans de paiement, chacun avec des paiements mensuels différents et des frais de fin.
- Régularisez votre accord à l'avance pour économiser sur les coûts d'intérêt.
]]>
        </fr>
    </description>
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="src/LeasingOptions.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/LeaseDeal.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/BuyVehicleDataExtension.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/ShopConfigScreenExtension.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/VehicleExtension.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/gui/NewFinanceFrame.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <l10n filenamePrefix="languages/l10n" />
</modDesc>