<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="100">
    <author>Ozz</author>
    <version>1.0.0.6</version>
    <iconFilename>icon_HirePurchasing.dds</iconFilename>
    <title>
        <en>Hire Purchasing</en>
        <de>Mietkauf</de>
        <fr>Location-Achat</fr>
		<uk>Оренда з правом викупу</uk>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[Hire Purchasing

A mod that adds an option to purchase equipment through a hire purchase model.

- Purchase equipment by putting down a configurable deposit. A higher deposit will reduce the interest rate.
- Choose how long your agreement should last.
- Choose from four payment plans, each with different monthly payments and final fees.
- Settle your agreement early to save on interest costs.

Github: https://github.com/sprkem/FS25_HirePurchasing

Changelog:

1.0.0.6
- Add totals to hire purchasing menu
- Add Ukrainian translation, thanks to Hunt3RSH
- Update PL translation

1.0.0.5
- Add Turkish translation, thanks to Cyber-Syntax
- Add Spanish translation, thanks to Daniel86ESP
- Add Chinese translation, thanks to NongDeChuanRen
- Add Polish translation, thanks to 00-Mario-00

1.0.0.4
- Reset choices to defaults when opening the dialog. Before, previously selected choices were carried forward.

1.0.0.3
- Fix the mod for multiplayer
- No longer shows hire purchase button when customising
- Add Brazilian translation, thanks to Onicaro
- Add Italian translation, thanks to FirenzeIT

1.0.0.2:
- Fix a bug when customizing a vehicle it could consider it sold and settle the hire purchase agreement
- Update German translation, thanks to redcaptm

1.0.0.1:
- Fix a bug when hire purchasing a vehicle with custom colors from the unlimited color configuation mod preventing save

]]>
        </en>
        <de><![CDATA[Mietkauf

Ein Mod, der eine Option zum Kauf von Ausrüstung über ein Ratenkaufmodell hinzufügt.

- Kaufe Ausrüstung mit einer konfigurablem Anzahlung. Eine höhere Anzahlung reduziert den Zinseszins.
- Wähle die Dauer deines Vertrags.
- Wähle aus vier Zahlungsplänen, jedes mit unterschiedlichen monatlichen Zahlungen und Endgebühren.
- Setze deinen Vertrag früh ab, um auf Zinskosten zu sparen.

Github: https://github.com/sprkem/FS25_HirePurchasing

Änderungsliste:

1.0.0.6
- Summen zum Mietkaufmenü hinzufügen
- Ukrainische Übersetzung hinzugefügt, dank Hunt3RSH
- Polnische Übersetzung aktualisiert

1.0.0.5
- Türkische Übersetzung hinzugefügt (dank Cyber-Syntax)
- Spanische Übersetzung hinzugefügt (dank Daniel86ESP)
- Chinesische Übersetzung hinzugefügt (dank NongDeChuanRen)
- Polnische Übersetzung hinzugefügt (dank 00-Mario-00)

1.0.0.4
- Auswahlmöglichkeiten werden beim Öffnen des Dialogs auf die Standardwerte zurückgesetzt. Zuvor wurden zuvor ausgewählte Optionen übernommen.

1.0.0.3
- Mod für Mehrspielermodus reparieren
- Beim Anpassen wird die Schaltfläche für den Ratenkauf nicht mehr angezeigt
- Brasilianische Übersetzung hinzugefügt, danke an Onicaro

1.0.0.2:
- Behebung eines Fehlers beim Anpassen eines Fahrzeugs, der dazu führte, dass es als verkauft galt und der Mietkaufvertrag abgewickelt wurde.
- Aktualisierung der deutschen Übersetzung, danke an redcaptm

1.0.0.1:
- Behebung eines Fehlers beim Mietkauf eines Fahrzeugs mit benutzerdefinierten Farben aus dem Mod „Unbegrenzte Farbkonfiguration“, der das Speichern verhinderte.

]]>
        </de>
        <fr><![CDATA[Location-Achat

Un mod qui ajoute une option d'achat d'équipement via un modèle de location-vente.

- Achetez des équipements en payant une cautionnable caution. Une plus grande caution réduit le taux d'intérêt.
- Choisissez la durée de votre accord.
- Choisissez parmi quatre plans de paiement, chacun avec des paiements mensuels différents et des frais de fin.
- Régularisez votre accord à l'avance pour économiser sur les coûts d'intérêt.

Github: https://github.com/sprkem/FS25_HirePurchasing

Journal des modifications:

1.0.0.6
- Ajout des totaux au menu de location-vente
- Ajout de la traduction ukrainienne, grâce à Hunt3RSH
- Mise à jour de la traduction PL

1.0.0.5
- Ajout de la traduction turque, grâce à Cyber-Syntax
- Ajout de la traduction espagnole, grâce à Daniel86ESP
- Ajout de la traduction chinoise, grâce à NongDeChuanRen
- Ajout de la traduction polonaise, grâce à 00-Mario-00

1.0.0.4
- Réinitialisation des choix aux valeurs par défaut lors de l'ouverture de la boîte de dialogue. Auparavant, les choix précédemment sélectionnés étaient conservés.

1.0.0.3
- Correction du mod multijoueur
- Le bouton de location-vente n'apparaît plus lors de la personnalisation
- Ajout de la traduction en brésilien, grâce à Onicaro

1.0.0.2:
- Correction d'un bug lors de la personnalisation d'un véhicule: celui-ci était considéré comme vendu et le contrat de location-vente était résilié.
- Mise à jour de la traduction allemande, merci à redcaptm

1.0.0.1:
- Correction d'un bug lors de la location-vente d'un véhicule avec des couleurs personnalisées grâce au mod de configuration de couleurs illimitées, empêchant la sauvegarde.

]]>
        </fr>
        <uk><![CDATA[Оренда з правом викупу
Модифікація, що додає можливість придбати обладнання за моделлю оренди з правом викупу (Лізинг).
- Придбайте обладнання, сплативши налаштовуваний завдаток. Чим вищий завдаток, тим нижча процентна ставка.
- Оберіть термін дії угоди.
- Оберіть один із чотирьох планів оплати, кожен із яких має різні щомісячні платежі та кінцевий платіж.
- Достроково розрахуйтеся за договором, щоб заощадити на відсотках.
Github: https://github.com/sprkem/FS25_HirePurchasing
Перелік змін:

1.0.0.5
- Додано турецький переклад, завдяки Cyber-Syntax.
- Додано іспанський переклад, завдяки Daniel86ESP.
- Додано китайський переклад, завдяки NongDeChuanRen.
- Додано польський переклад, завдяки 00-Mario-00.
- Додано український переклад, завдяки Hunt3R.

1.0.0.4
- Скидання вибору до стандартних налаштувань при відкритті діалогового вікна. Раніше раніше вибрані варіанти зберігалися.

1.0.0.3
- Виправлення модифікації для багатокористувацького режиму.
- Більше не відображається кнопка купівлі в розстрочку під час налаштування.
- Додано бразильський переклад, завдяки Onicaro.
- Додано італійський переклад, завдяки FirenzeIT.

1.0.0.2:
- Виправлено помилку, коли під час налаштування транспортного засобу його можна було вважати проданим і укласти договір про купівлю в розстрочку.
- Оновлено німецький переклад, завдяки redcaptm.

1.0.0.1:
- Виправлено помилку, коли купівля в розстрочку транспортного засобу з індивідуальними кольорами з модом необмеженої конфігурації кольорів заважала збереженню.

]]>
        </uk>
    </description>
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="src/BuyVehicleDataExtension.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/LeaseDeal.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/LeasingOptions.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/ShopConfigScreenExtension.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/VehicleExtension.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/gui/NewFinanceFrame.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/events/InitialClientStateEvent.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/events/NewLeaseDealEvent.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/events/ObjectIdChangedEvent.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <l10n filenamePrefix="languages/l10n" />
</modDesc>